JUSTIN BROWN

justinbrowncodes.github.io | justinjbrown23@gmail.com

Summary

Skilled Software Engineer with a strong background in programming and mathematics. Experienced in exploratory data analysis, building machine learning models, and evaluating through various metrics. Motivated to collaborate with team members and optimize systems to meet specifications. Proficient in presenting data/concepts clearly and creatively.

Skills

- Numpy, Pandas
- Scikit-Learn, Keras
- Tensorflow, Pytorch
- Matplotlib, Seaborn

- Python
- MatLab
- C++ / Java
- HTML/CSS

- Git version control
- Unix
- Jupyter Notebooks
- SQL

Experience

Software Developer

FSU Program in Neuroscience (Vincis Lab)

08/2018 to 03/2020

Tallahassee. FL

- Utilized MATLAB and Python to program neuroscience software for controlling experiments.
- Implemented deep learning models to estimate pupil dilation, reduced the need for other costly methods for collecting neural activity.
- Worked with Principle Investigator to plan, code, and present projects from start to finish.
- Modified lab website to update profiles and implement different API's.

Building Manager Trainee FSU Oglesby Union Guest Services

12/2017 to 07/2018

Tallahassee, FL

Assisted with organization and setup for union reservations and FSU ballroom events.

Certifications

IIII Al Engineering Professional

2020

Advanced Machine Learning and Signal Processing

2020

Python Data Structures

2020

Education

Computer Science, Physics, Mathematics

Florida State University

2015-2019

Tallahassee, FL

High School Diploma

Suncoast Community High School

2015 Riviera Beach, FL

• Completed professional development of Android Applications in Java

Extracurricular Activities

FSU Cell and Molecular Biology Graduate Student Association

April 2020

- Developed and Led presentation: "Intro to Neural Networks: Machine Learning with Python".
- Explained process of a neural network and demonstrated the A.I. using a self-developed game.

Kaggle 2020

Submitted machine learning solutions to complex data science projects.

TechNole 2017 to 2018

Competed in MLH (Major League Hacking) competitions at FSU and Georgia Tech.